(Production Sponsors)
(Ministry of Culture, Sports and Tourism and KOCCA)
(This is a work of fiction. All names, characters, )
(and incidents are products of the author's imagination.)
(All child actors were accompanied by a guardian, )
(and filmed in accordance with labour laws.)
(15th Century, Joseon)
It is morning already.
All I want for my lord,
who saw potential in this humble servant,
is to bring him joy.
You summoned me, a mere commoner,
to your royal presence,
and ordered me to strengthen Joseon through technological advancement.
I humbly bow to accept your command.
A position that had no name.
If there are more people like me in the future,
what would we be called?
To open...
and to develop.
Someone who opens up new possibilities.
A person who develops and makes them a reality.
Yes, that is it.
"Developer" would be the perfect name.
Your Highness, the Crown Prince!
What is the meaning of this!
This is the only Honcheonui blueprint.
Your Royal Highness.
You pathetic fool.
Yeong Sil.
Pay him no mind.
Your Majesty.
Seeing today's great laptop tragedy, I got this idea for a web novel.
A poignant friendship between King Sejong and Jang Yeong Sil,
and the Crown Prince, his enemy, has great chemistry with Yeong Sil.
My ears are bleeding. Na Rae, are you trying to get sued?
Seriously. A genius who transcended class...
to fall for such a pathetic prince.
It's an insult.
Send an angry emoticon.
I wouldn't call him dim-witted. Crown Prince Munjong was brilliant.
Right, the Cheugugi was actually Munjong's idea.
The prince from my story is actually based on Grand Prince Suyang...
But why did you use my face and San's for the characters?
Because you two are the hottest engineers I know!
So, are you skipping the group blind date?
Why would you even ask when you know I'm not into that?
Not you, Yeon San!
How can you even ask that...
when you know the state San's in today?
(Number one on XXX)
You actually came, Min Hak.
Of course.
You were great out there earlier.
Careful.
(LOVE.exe)
(Episode 3: New Semester Promo)
(Eight Hours Earlier)
- It's mine! - Mine! Mine!
Everyone, quiet down, please!
Alright, time for my daily good deed for the environment...
I told you it was mine.
I clearly said it was mine.
Besides, you can obviously see it's a different laptop!
To be fair, it looked just the same a second ago.
Let's get the council room bullhorn.
If we wait, they'll walk all over us.
Wait, the thing is...
that the matter of who's at fault is a bit unclear.
Hey, where's our rookie?
If you're talking about responsibility,
I clearly said it was mine and was approaching to get it,
but your security guard forcibly stopped me.
Now, I understand that,
because these fans were shouting, "He's mine,"
he mistook me for one of them. I'll grant you that.
But in all that chaos, what was I supposed to...
I'm really grateful for my fans,
but hearing "he's mine" can be a little suffocating sometimes.
I wonder if she's one of your fans, too?
Or maybe not?
Then she could be one of your fans, Jinny.
That's it, she's one of your fans! Right?
It must've been "Jinny's mine" then. Not "Min Hak's mine."
Gosh, what is wrong with me?
I'm so full of myself, aren't I?
Stop laughing.
Wipe that soda up so it's not sticky.
- Gosh, what a mess. - Is this supposed to shut me up?
Won't that do?
I'm even paying for this out of my own pocket.
Your own pocket? The rookie staffer's own pocket?
Hold on, Yeon San.
As I'm responsible for this space, I can't let this injustice slide.
Who are you?
I'm the Emergency Chair of the Computer Engineering Department.
- Who's in charge here? - That's you!
- Yes? - You broke someone's property,
and you're making the rookie pay?
I'm not the one who broke it.
So what? Why should the person with the least authority pay for it?
Shouldn't their bosses cover this? That's why they're paid more, right?
All right, who's the producer here?
We need to get back to filming,
so let's talk about this after we wrap up.
For now, could you please step aside?
I'm not moving an inch until someone takes responsibility.
Everyone! Scrum!
Scrum!
Do you know who that tall, dashing woman over there is?
Her?
She's Kang Dong Won, the CS chair,
Your Majesty.
Her real name is Kang Dong Won.
But her nickname is also "Kang Dong Won from Engineering."
Interesting.
Kang Dong Won.
Heads of Hair and Makeup, can I have you for a moment?
Hey, Jinny.
Oh, gosh.
Didn't I tell you to always be careful when you're mic'd?
Sorry. But hey,
I was just wondering what your schedule was like after this.
There's a screening I have to go to in Yongsan.
Director Cha Nook invited me.
What about tomorrow? Are you free tomorrow?
Just tell me now.
It's just the two of us here.
The thing is...
Min Hak.
I think we need to make a change.
Really?
That's exactly what I was going to tell you.
- You were? - Yes.
I think it's time for us to take the next step.
Exactly! The next step!
To advance in our careers, we can't afford to be complacent.
We have to look toward the future.
Gosh.
I was a little nervous about this.
But it turns out we're on the same page.
So what should we do?
When should we go public?
Go public? With what?
What?
You said "next step," so I just assumed...
Okay. Keeping it private is fine too.
It would just be a headache for you if people found out anyway.
Min Hak. I was saying we should end things.
For good.
You and I are just friends.
You're no idol or actor, Min Hak, so you're not even a coworker.
We're just...
someone who was just passing through my life...
Just passing through...
But we kissed...
That was just a happening.
We're both young and beautiful. Things happen, right?
Maybe if it was once, but three times is...
And what's more, last week we...
No. Look, Min Hak.
Our careers are on shaky ground.
We could vanish and nobody would care.
I'm an actress, and my best credit? Honestly?
It's that "Like Dew" soju commercial.
And you're just a semi-celebrity who started on "Match on Wheels."
Don't you think we both need to take that next step?
So...
you're saying I'm not your next one.
I'm going to the US this fall.
It's for a streaming original film.
You know my biggest dream, right?
To be bigger than Jung Ho Yeon and make your mark in Hollywood.
Yes, exactly. I want that more than anything.
Not Jinny, the washed-up idol, but Jinny, the global superstar.
That's really awesome.
From our own respective places,
you, right where you are,
and me, right where I am.
Let's each do our absolute best,
and raise our worth, our value,
and then meet again, Min Hak.
Doing our best on our own for now.
What she's saying is so complicated.
And she's using so much English.
Okay, we can't just stand around here all day.
So you two, just settle it with rock-paper-scissors.
- What? - One of you two has to pay for it.
Or just split it fifty-fifty.
Come on. Rock-paper-scissors.
- Go on. - Ready?
If you don't throw, you lose. Rock-paper-scissors!
Wait a minute.
I'll pay for it.
What? Why would you, Min Hak?
I'm the one who broke the laptop, so I should pay for it.
Are you okay? Don't cry. It's my fault. I'm sorry.
How much do I owe you?
Alright, let's run the numbers, shall we?
You spectacularly wrecked this new 2025 laptop.
With an Intel Core Ultra 200HX CPU and a GeForce RTX 5070 GPU.
Those two components alone are well over 3,000 dollars,
plus three 1-terabyte SSDs in a Super RAID 5 configuration.
Those run 170 dollars a piece, totalling 510 dollars.
Importantly, with data recovery, the grand total is...
Hold on a second.
I need a calculator.
And that amount I just quoted?
That's not even including compensation for my inconvenience...
while the laptop contents are being recovered.
And if the recovery is impossible,
then there's the priceless value, which is incalculable.
- Three hundred thirty times... - Forget it.
Just give me your number.
I'll send you the official estimate,
and you can wire the money right over.
Okay.
Gosh, did you see that? San got Kang Min Hak's number.
- Was that her plan? - Wait!
No. I can't allow that.
I'm his manager, so please talk to me.
As long as someone is responsible, I don't care who.
Here.
This will work, right?
Min Hak, Jinny's team is panicking because we're delayed.
What? Right.
Let's go.
I'll draw up the estimate and will be in contact!
Were you about to give her your number?
Good thing I was there to stop you.
That's how you get psycho stalkers.
They shout, "He's mine!" Don't you know that?
I don't think she's like that.
Besides,
I have to take responsibility for my own actions.
I know. You're so responsible and naive.
That's why I'm here, to protect you. See?
- I know, and I'm always grateful. - So, did you ask Jinny about it?
Well...
I didn't get a chance to bring up the drama.
Why not? What were you so busy talking about?
What I mean is that if Jinny recommends you for it,
it's a natural and great opportunity.
Excuse me, Min Hak?
I didn't get to say a proper hello earlier.
Min Hak, thank you so much.
Don't mention it.
Min Hak, go get your touch-up now. You know where to go, right?
- Right now? - Yes. Go to the hall by the corner.
Excuse me. One second.
You really went through it earlier.
No. I'm grateful to him, but I feel bad.
He's just a genuinely good-hearted person.
But people online twist things and say his head's in the clouds.
Some people just love to trash him.
I'm worried that this whole laptop incident...
will also start a rumour.
Should I post something online to stop those kinds of rumours?
I'll write that he's a total angel, a saviour, a prince!
Gosh, you don't have to do all that.
Maybe don't exaggerate quite that much.
Just stick to the facts. Like you said, an angel, a saviour...
Could you post that somewhere for us?
- Of course. - Right.
I have a video of what happened.
Should I send you a screenshot?
- Yes, that'd be great. - Yes.
Great.
Isn't this a blessing in disguise?
You might get a new laptop from this.
But she hadn't backed it up.
Her high school data is on there.
I'm heading to a data recovery center first.
If it weren't for that brainless fool...
Excuse me.
Yes?
Sorry, it's just been bugging me.
I'm sure I've seen you somewhere.
I don't think so. Like I said, I'm not a fan or...
Now he's going to say, "Are you Ahn In Dae?" again.
I guess I just have one of those faces.
We have no connection, so please just go on your way.
I'll contact your manager about the repair estimate.
I knew it.
- You're a fan of Jinny's? - What?
I can tell by how indifferent you've been to me.
By the way, good job just now. Making up with those staff members.
What are you talking about?
I don't mean to criticize, but if you're too harsh with staff,
you know, it can make your celebrity look bad.
So on Jinny's behalf, I'd like to thank...
Should I rip his head off?
If you want to film something, I could do a reel with you.
What do you say?
I want to crack his head open and see what's inside.
What could possibly be going on in a head like that?
(Yongsan)
Who knows. But I can't tell if this is even recoverable.
So...
you rushed all the way to Yongsan this late at night for this?
That's why I need you to recover it, no matter what.
I'll have something to share in two weeks.
Two weeks?
It's going to cost you 800 dollars.
But for an extra 200 dollars,
I might be able to get it done a week faster.
That's a lot more than what it said online.
For water damage, I'd charge 300 and call it a day.
But this wasn't water. It was a sugary drink.
What difference does that make?
Your follow-up care was all wrong.
And it's a one-terabyte drive,
which is double the size of most laptops.
Plus, the newer models are a lot trickier to work on.
- I'll pay once it's recovered. - Payment is upfront.
Look, I'm doing the work regardless.
The price is for my labour.
Fine.
It's not like I'm the one who'll be footing the bill anyway.
(Hangang University)
You could've just used a hand double for the laptop shot.
Hey, where's Jinny?
She filmed her part and left two hours ago.
It wasn't even a cameo.
Said she had to go to a screening.
So you were stuck waiting forever for no reason.
I'm fine.
We didn't have anything scheduled afterwards anyway.
You're too nice for your own good.
Let's go. You're heading home, right?
It's about the laptop from earlier. I've taken it in for repairs.
I'll let you know as soon as I get the estimate.
Hey, I'm going to go meet up with a friend real quick.
A friend? All of a sudden? Who?
- Do Not Answer. - Well...
- Min Hak. - Yes?
Look, I don't care who you meet.
Stay out of trouble, and we're good.
You get me? I'm trusting you.
Thanks.
I'll drop you off.
Seriously? You won't pick up?
These jerks must be on social media.
Let's see, his handle is...
What a pain.
I swore to never use SNS again, but I guess I'll have to send a DM.
What the heck?
Kang Min Hak bought a pricey laptop to cover for a staffer's mistake.
I heard there was an ad shoot on campus, so I went to watch.
Jinny and Kang Min Hak are stunning.
A laptop got snapped in half. A staffer confused it with a prop.
The laptop owner made a huge scene.
He said the staffer wasn't at fault, but his own.
- He's an angel, a saviour, a prince. - A prince.
So he breaks my laptop, ghosts me, and now he gets to be the hero?
(Yongsan Electronics Market, Sinyongsan Station)
It's so chaotic. Darn it.
My Tuna.
How much did you drink?
What took you so long? I was dying to see you.
Sorry. Let's go.
Gosh! You're drunk. Let's go.
Come on. Let's go.
No, I don't want to go. Let's just stay a little longer.
Cheers!
Let's stay a little longer.
You like the student council more than me, don't you?
- Come on, let's go. - Go where? You're so mean.
Come on, guys. Aren't you bored?
It's been forever since my last blind date.
Let's liven things up! Okay, "Timing Game"! One!
- Two! - Three!
- Four! - Five!
- Drink up! - I'll be your Black Knight.
- Come on. - What's this?
Come on. Seriously?
- Timing Game! One! - Two!
- Three! -Three!
Okay!
Drink up.
- Hey. - Drink up.
- Let me get this one. I'm serious. - Come on.
- Oh, boy. - Unbelievable.
He can't even handle his liquor.
I mean, come on.
Gosh, look at him go.
You can really hold your liquor.
I'm sending you that repair bill as soon as I can, no matter how.
That darn Kang Min Hak!
If this is just a simulation, may its developer be cursed too.
This is nice.
If someone breaks up with you and then calls you at night,
you're supposed to just ignore them.
Even if they're drunk, begging you to come over,
just turn off your phone.
How could I do that?
What if the next day I pretended I didn't remember anything...
and say I never asked you to come over?
Then I'd just think, "I guess she didn't call me."
Why bother? Why go to all that trouble for me?
You're so sweet, Min Hak.
You're not like your dad.
You could never be like him.
Never ever.
You should get some sleep, Jinny.
You're so cute. My Min Hak.
Focus on me.
But your phone's ringing.
Hello?
Really?
So who's there?
I don't think I know them.
I'll call you back.
Hey, I think I have to go.
Apparently, Amy says the directors...
and the foreign guests are waiting for me.
But I haven't even finished watching the movie.
What should I do?
You should go, then.
Sorry.
Want to rest here for a bit?
I'm okay.
Jinny, you reek of alcohol.
I'll head out first,
so you can take your time getting ready.
Okay.
That kid's head is in the clouds, and that manager's a total scammer.
I'll just use my anonymous account to bring justice down on you two.
But I'll be reasonable about it.
"Awaiting response for laptop cost."
Darn it. This battery issue again...
Excuse me.
What are the odds of this encounter?
Is the creator of this game...
just a developer who is obsessed with encounters?
Freeze!
Hey, wait, hold on!
Hey, you! Look at this!
How can you just walk away like that...
What am I supposed to do if...
I knew you wouldn't just let me walk away.
Hey, let go of me.
What are you doing? Let go.
Why?
Hey, I said let go! How dare you just grab and hug me?
I'm sorry. The noise cancellation on my headphones works so well...
- You're the girl from before. - Yes. The one from...
- You were really an obsessive fan? - An obsessive fan?
So this is what it's like. They just follow you all day.
Seriously?
As I told you before,
being like this won't help your celebrity.
If you truly care about someone,
you need to know when to let go. Got it?
Let go of what?
Why don't you let go of some cash for my laptop?
What's her problem?
Gosh.
Hey, where are you going?
Who's a fan of who? You think the world's your fan club?
I wish that weren't the case,
but we keep running into each other, day and night.
On top of that, it's from Gyeonggi Province to Yongsan.
And before that, too.
We've seen each other around before. Right?
The reason you think you've seen me is because you have!
We're in the same department!
That ridiculously named...
Converged Physical Technology and Global Content Development major!
We keep meeting on our small, and now even smaller, campus.
Do you even remember the laptop you broke today?
You bent it, poured soda over it,
and tried drying it with a hairdryer!
I need it for my job, my schoolwork, and a competition,
which is why I came to the electronics mecca,
all the way to Yongsan!
And what? A fan? An obsessive fan?
So it's okay to just grab and hug any fan you see?
Now I get it. I completely misunderstood.
You're just figuring that out now?
It's kind of a long story.
So why isn't your manager picking up his phone?
I had no idea he wasn't picking up. I'm sorry.
But I really have to go now, so if you give me your number...
I don't trust you anymore.
Yes, that's fair.
Then if you give me your phone, I'll put my number in for you.
My battery's dead.
Dead...
Then do you have any paper?
I promise I'll contact you.
My repair estimate!
Hey, the numbers are all smudged! Hey, stop!
Wait a second!
Get out of the way!
What do you think you're doing?
I couldn't just let you get hurt.
Right. And for a second...
- Someone call for a ride? - I didn't!
Well, you were shouting "Stop," so I thought...
Anyone here going to Gangnam?
- Coming through. - Yes, go ahead.
The group blind date today totally bombed.
Is a bad date supposed to be news?
When my day...
Gosh, I always think my dry spell would end...
at the start of every semester.
These guys won't even reply to me.
Darn it...
And look at me, just watching dramas about guys falling in love.
Okay. Now, less bicep, more trap.
Yes, those traps are looking tasty. Let's feed them.
That's it.
Hey, you!
You know these walls are paper-thin.
What was that about something tasty?
Sorry. My personal training session was scheduled for tonight.
No, wait, what? Who does personal training at home?
You seem to go to our school. Let's try to be more considerate.
Okay. I'm sorry. We'll be quiet now.
Come on.
All right, push it all the way up!
Okay. All right, feel the burn.
Okay.
Oh, that's good.
I need to de-stress.
Should I watch "The Demon Slayer" that Finnish drama?
No. Lego ASMR.
Or maybe I should just get to work first?
There are thousands of reasons why a bug might occur.
You might have missed a use case or used the wrong formula.
Why would they send me this?
I'm telling you, it's not a hardware problem.
Or you went outside the memory area allocated for the program,
applied the wrong operation to the data,
or you failed to check if the user input was valid.
(Park Chang Yi)
San, long time no see.
Or, like the moth that flew into Grace Hopper's computer,
it's because something got in that shouldn't have.
What are you doing here?
I came here to apologise.
How did you know where I live?
The dean told me.
Is he even allowed to do that?
I'm a little wet from the rain. Mind if I take this off?
Yes, I do mind.
Darn it.
Joo Yeon San.
Why aren't you answering me?
What?
What's Python?
- What? - This.
It's a programming language.
A language?
It's more dynamic and concise than other languages.
And it's highly readable.
So it's great for everyone, from beginners to experts.
So even beginners can use it?
And it's dynamic?
Concise doesn't necessarily mean easy.
But it's compatible with a lot of different operating systems.
So they can connect with each other?
Like us?
Even though we're different?
Which is why it's highly scalable.
Can I kiss you?
Did you hear me?
Processing.
(Python Hacking Program)
Should I put it in now?
No, not yet. It's just...
Gosh, this is definitely rated R.
- Wait. This is too racy! - What?
- Is this okay? - I mean, can we even air this?
What is this?
It's something you like.
I'm putting it in.
Here it goes.
I know you like it.
I'm putting it in, okay?
- He's putting it in! He's doing it! - What in the world...
Gosh. It's fizzing up.
Gosh, it's really fizzing up!
- Gosh, look at all those bubbles! - It's a bubble party!
They're clothed, flirting in a tub, so why is my heart fluttering?
He's really going all out. This is insane.
- Wait, isn't this getting racy? - Are you okay with this?
- Oh my gosh. - It's cute.
Isn't this a little too much?
No, it's not. He's leading so well...
- to ensure she's comfortable. - What?
Why would I have a dream like that?
Okay. It's been a long week,
and I'm only human, a creature of flesh, blood, and passion.
Meeting him in person, the video's audio,
and the memory of that darn encounter in Yongsan...
All these inputs were simply reflected in my dream...
and supposedly prove the app's theory which is...
a load of bull!